and then we went to court and we just
got that over with because I know
sometimes divorces they can linger
listen they'd be lasting for like three
years yeah I was like I'm not doing that
on the paper no
um at the end I wasn't really like
satisfied with the agreement we came to
but that's how much I just wanted it to
be over with I was like I'm not about to
do this any longer
[Music]
so funky welcome to another episode of
small doses podcast
I am joined today all legs
um by BNB this is actually pretty cool
because we've never met in person right
but we like chit chat I feel like you're
my girl
we like chit chat on the IG and I feel
like I really genuinely
I have no desire to be a parent but zero
I parented enough yeah from a distance
but like literally watching you with
your kids is like a master class I'd be
like how is she so girl calm what is it
I don't know and people think I smoke
weed and I don't
I don't know what it is I think it's
probably like I'm starting to realize
that my calmness and me being so passive
when it comes to a lot of things is
probably like um
um due to like some
trauma in my life for real like and
that's I know that sounds dramatic but
it doesn't sounds normal yeah because I
just started to realize this year like
people are like you've let stuff go like
so much and I think if I just keep going
and don't have to deal with it I just be
like whatever whatever like I don't get
offended by much and that's not a good
thing I was gonna say It's Gonna Catch
You yeah it's not a good thing well how
old are you
let's not talk about that right here
because we've been having some issues
with
um I know you ain't really been watching
all this stuff but
um people have been like going okay my
mother-in-law right I'm suing her for
defamation of character because she just
literally said two days ago that I use
the fake ID when I went to jail and gave
them the wrong age and she's just making
a big thing out of so yeah let's just
okay yeah I know that's a lot too I just
can't we all get them no we cannot ma'am
okay we are we are suing people
yeah yeah
we're suing family yeah that's it and
it's bad because again like I pride
myself on just being out the way staying
out the way and with everything that's
going on right now they're making it
impossible for me to stay out the way
like you know I'm in a vlog every other
day because
you know well I can't even imagine I
mean going through a divorce in itself
is very difficult it's very painful like
I mean I
can only imagine also there's kids
involved but then when the Public's
involved it goes to another level
absolutely another level and then just
imagine well not really imagine but
literally trying to like get through a
divorce with three small children on a
day-to-day basis and make things as
normal as possible for them but then
it's still like the extra drama that's
coming with it like it's it's insane
like I'm like I I didn't really have
time to
like grieve you know what I'm saying
like because even though I did want the
divorce and I wanted like it's still
like you know my family is just no you
can do things to be true at the same
time like you can know that something is
the right thing yeah but also grieve
that it was the wrong thing absolutely
right like because that's the part that
sucks you like I know this is what's
supposed to happen but it sucks that
this is what's supposed to happen yeah
like and that's really what's happening
and it was
I don't want to say it was but it has
been and it still kind of is like some
days just really difficult because I'm
like I'm trying to get away from that
and like establish like some peace you
know and structure for me and my kids
and it's just like
you know well you know the thing about
trauma too is that it's funny that you
said you feel like you respond to trauma
like because of trauma you respond to
things like real like placidly there's
the opposite right where a lot of people
respond to trauma by chaos yep like they
just need chaos yes because it makes
them feel it's like a I have a working
theory that I'm sure has already been
proven and there are probably actually
like written studies about this in
journals but I'm just talking in the
small doses version of things I have a
theory that like
you know the same way that we have like
chemical
um our body does chemical reactions to
like drugs and that's what then causes
the addiction we have those same
chemical reactions with people with
situations Etc and so our body is just
like addicted to certain things like
it's just comfortable and so it seeks
out trying to like get to that even
though it's not the best thing for you
oh absolutely and I I strongly believe
that outside of like certain drama and
Chaos some people they just they don't
know who they are outside of that stuff
they just like all right well it's too
calm yeah we're doing what's going on
who needs me right yeah yeah and it
sucks it really does because I would
love to just live a very peaceful life
soft girl era absolutely you know I say
that but at the same time I'll be like
trying to fix like and carrying stuff up
the stairs that's still soft girl
to me software era isn't like you know
isn't no I'm not going to assemble this
couch you know or whatever but software
era to me is just not feeling like you
have to Buck Up yeah all the time like I
feel like there's a lot of me that for a
long time just was yeah like ready right
you know and then you're like this is
tiring yeah let me relax I thought a
meme the other day that said success is
a calm nervous system
um that is the one right there seriously
and that was that is the one I need to
meditate on that yes I love that because
that's really the goal yeah you know
what I'm saying to be
and a relaxed State and not waking up
and looking around what's going on
what's going on today so tell me this
you you said you know you came to me you
said I want to tell my story yeah I want
to tell it in a sophisticated
environment yeah which you see I'm
sophisticated
I may have to serve tea
so I would love for you to so start from
the beginning like what is the story
that you feel like you want to tell and
you want to be able to tell with me so
the thing is I feel like I'm kind of
like outgrowing the audience like the
consumers of the show that I'm on so
when things are happening on the show
they are following it in a different
type of way it's like they're confused
about certain things and you know
because I am going through a divorce and
I've been
um what they've been showing on the show
is like people are just like oh my gosh
she's so bitter she's so miserable and
she's trying to drag her friends into
this stuff with her and I'm just like
where are you seeing that because for
one
um I filed for divorce this year well
last year in November and our divorce
was finalized in June
so before our show started to air I had
filed for divorce I was trying to keep
things very like quiet I just wanted to
get it over with and then as soon as the
show started
um the woman that he like cheated on me
with I heard that he was like bringing
her on the show so at that point I was
like okay well we're gonna have to talk
about this now because at first I wasn't
planning on even addressing the fact
that he cheated or who he cheated with I
was just gonna leave it alone and keep
it moving so he brought the girl on the
show and then you know he brought his
baby mama on the show and
um I just started being like attacked in
the midst of like going through a
divorce so like all these women
including his mom
you know they just started coming out
the Woodworks just like why do you feel
like they just all because I feel like
that's been part of the narrative like
this whole time right but they'd be
coming for bands yeah but what is that
about well I think um
so about scrap like when I first met him
I was I admired the fact that he um
he didn't hold grudges against people he
would tell me like some crazy things
that people had done to him and you know
over the course of his life and he would
see these people and be cool with him
and all this and I'm like wow like I
should be more like that but over time I
was just like you just ain't got no
boundaries you know what I'm saying so
you let people do all this to you and
then you just you know what I'm saying
you invite them back into your life but
especially when something is going on
and he needs he feels like he needs like
a tribe A Tribe and and that's what it
was like he gathered his tribe of people
who had in the past tried to tear him
apart completely you know these are
women who said some of the craziest
things about him and he just you know
are teaming up with them now which is
crazy to me
um because I mean it's no secret people
know like they both both abuse I mean
accused him of being like abusive in
like relationships and now they're just
like
with him and like come in for me and
it's it's real confusing because I'm
like you are standing here next to these
same women who have like accused you of
some of the most
heinous yes and and then there's the
daughter next to him even though they've
accused him and that's the thing about
women to me too I'm like
you've had all these women you know kind
of like feeling for you like when you
were alleging these things and just to
turn around and spin the block you know
you know it's really crazy because it's
also on television so it's hard to know
what's real yeah what's not that's why
when you were saying like you know the
fans are are watching things happening
but they're happening like out of order
yeah you know and it's like folks can't
discern that's to me that's a tricky
part with reality TV absolutely folks
can't discern which part of it is
reality and which part is reality right
right yeah but then you're living both
of it
so what what even what do you feel like
was the final straw that made you say
I'm a file for divorce so the final
straw was
um him cheating and the person that it
was with it was like a x and he was on
the Millennium tour and his ex was on
the tour as well
and it was a little we had a little
discussion about it before the tour
started I'm like you know this may be a
little like awkward uncomfortable and
he's like well no like it's fine and you
can just come like on the entire tour
and I'm like I'm not gonna come babysit
you you know what I'm saying like I sh I
have three kids and so um but we did
have some issues going on already and
then when I saw that that had happened
the very next day after I saw that um
you know I looked at his phone and saw
like text messages and DMS and all this
and the very next day I filed for
divorce like it was just no
conversation needed after that
what is it about
because this is not the first time he's
cheated
um well as far as I know it's the first
time you know got you okay that's fair
yeah um what is it though
because I feel like we've all been in
these scenarios where we'll be like
there were problems right but then
there's like a final straw yeah what do
you feel like
kept you all together before the final
straw well I felt like he I didn't think
that he was a cheater I never considered
him like a cheater you know um he would
he was just very present like you know
we always did family stuff we had our
little back and forth and you know
sometimes he would go in the basement
and I would go over here but it was fine
because neither one of us had or to my
knowledge stepped outside of the
marriage but when we're having these
issues and then his mom is like being
crazy on the internet and saying weird
stuff on TV and he's not defending me
um that was just like the final straw
for me I'm like okay so you letting all
these people come at me and say all this
crazy stuff and then you're cheating on
top of that
yeah no
did you all ever go to couples therapy
we started therapy um probably maybe
like three months before
um I'll filed for divorce and it was
actually going pretty good or I thought
what did you like about it I like the
fact that it was just like a a space
where we could hear each other opposed
to
we we needed a mediator in between us
when we would have conversation I'm very
gentle with anybody in my life like
friends family anybody that I talk to
I'm very calm um and he just couldn't
receive that interesting he could not
you know what that is a common Trope
I've experienced this yes I did I didn't
think that that is a common thing it's
like it's so it's this goes back to my
theory I think some people they need the
argument yeah they need the argument
they I don't know if it's the chaos or
what but there's like something that
their body is like trying to get to and
even if you just stay calm and stay calm
and stay calm they're so like you know
we need to get to that and then
eventually
when it gets to that it gets to that and
then I'm the crazy person every time
every issue look at you yeah look at you
with your emotions I'm like this is what
I want to call Deborah Cox so she could
come in here and sing how did we get hit
yes you put it in the GPS and you drove
me to crazy absolutely yeah but I mean
for whatever reason the women
of the world
will take all of this in and I'm still
the problem
I'm still the problem no matter
how you spend it too many of us are con
are conditioned right to
default to protecting a man's ego
um and what I found was like the best
Brothers in my life is that they have
come to realize in their own Evolution
that it is up to no one to protect their
ego but themselves right and so like I
have a lot of homeboys I'm really
blessed to have a lot of homeboys who
have like gone through this like
self-exploration of like oh
hold up if I want to be a good dude
I gotta like figure that out for myself
because the world ain't training me how
to be a good dude exactly but it trains
women how to take care of men yeah and
so if you look like you're not doing
that in some way I feel like you really
take the L yeah you really do and and I
feel like you take the L either way
because our relationship was based on me
just like coddling him like in the
beginning it was just overly like
I'll rub your feet cook your food rub
your back do like I mean I didn't have
any problem with none of that stuff I
never did but then when I started having
kids and kids and taking care of the you
have to take care of the kids and I have
to take care of me and I also have to
work like there was never a time
um after I had any of my kids that I
took time off from work I'm gonna say
something the internet is going to be
mad at okay and scrap gonna be mad at it
too he probably gonna text me okay
so he did not have his mother
as a child and so you were mothering him
yeah in the ways that his mother did not
mother yeah and his mother is now
present in the way that she is but that
that developmental time she wasn't
present there right and so many of us
are mothering the men that we're with
yeah and then we realized at a certain
point either because we have children or
because we decide we don't want to have
children that we don't want a mother in
that way yeah and then it feels like how
dare you yep and and that's why I took
a lot of accountability for that because
I I did understand I'm like I I did a
lot I feel you a lot and nobody asked me
to you know what I'm saying I know that
I did that you know and I just didn't
have the capacity to do it any longer to
that extent you know what I'm saying
like I still try but it was just like
whenever I got a moment I wanted to just
be like
you know just like
just a moment you know and I listen like
I've never
tried to say that he was not like a a
great like Dad and we have some great
times like together like absolutely
um by no means have I ever tried to bash
him
um and you know he did things like we'll
take the kids in the morning so I can
get some extra rest but it still is
different because if the kids are in the
house
and I'm trying to nap I'm like halfway
napping because I'm like what they doing
am I gonna need to come down there is
somebody's gonna come up here so I mean
he I'm
he did some some really nice things he
was trying you know
um but I think when we started filming
it was just like a lot of emotion
um on both ends because you know he
didn't want the divorce I that was going
to be my next question did he want the
divorce no he didn't want the divorce
and I actually thought about trying to
reconcile but I know me and I'm like
I'm not gonna get over this the trust
yeah I'm not gonna get past that I just
knew that I wasn't so I was like I'm not
even gonna set him or me up for this
because I'm not gonna be going through
your phone I'm not gonna I'm just not
gonna do that for the rest of my life so
what ultimately made you go through the
phone so I just had a feeling
um that stuff going through the phone is
a that's a strong step oh yeah for sure
and I mean listen we were married for
five years and out of those five years
that was my second time going through
his phone and so
um this time it was just I was just
feeling some weird Vibes with him being
on this tour and the way that he was
interacting with this girl from the
first day of the tour to like the last
few dates of the tour I was like this is
this seems a little weird to me
and you know we be we be knowing
exactly you'd be knowing
that was cool how you did that right
there I didn't see it coming and it was
like bam I was spinning trying to throw
that
um ignorance in there somewhere
no I hate this for you though yeah no
it's it's cool though I mean it's not
cool the reason why I hate it right yeah
because it's like
I know so many sisters right now who are
going through breakups and divorces and
it's all for
very similar reason for the same reasons
like so even though there was infidelity
I feel like it's the cause the root
cause of the infidelity that ends up
being the actual reason right and a lot
of times the root cause is something as
basic as just like insecurity and the
insecurity can come first like so many
reasons that you can't even like clock
it yeah you know yeah but I actually
like
you know I'm so
self-aware and just aware right and and
I feel like
I feel people you know I I be
understanding what's your sign a Pisces
oh so so like I'm very understanding and
I saw what happened so he started this
tour right and
throughout our whole relationship he was
like trying to work towards getting back
into that space where he was before as
an artist right right yeah so he got on
this tour and you already know the story
yeah it was just like exciting for him
you know to see all those people every
night and I'm still on the phone with
him like yeah um the kids yeah
we got this going on you know I got a
doctor's appointment tomorrow and so
life was life in for me and when he was
on tour it was just like a fairy tale
you know and I understood like you know
the girls was just out there just like
oh my God and I'm at home like all right
so what we doing you know what I'm
saying
and he kind of he needs that though he
needs constant validation and I know
that you know he cannot survive without
somebody constantly saying oh my God
you're so amazing you look so good
you're doing so good because he's you
know yeah
he can't it's the trauma he will perish
honey it's but he is he is I mean I I
don't even want to just call it for
scrap because that really is so many
because
so many of our brothers just really well
so many of us right leaders didn't get
the attentiveness that we needed at the
like real like important time that we
needed it which is why when I was
watching with your kids I'm so intrigued
because your attentiveness is like you
just I mean you're like a tree just like
yes I feel like the tree climbing I'm
like look at that look at them but
you're still like giving each of them
what they what I'm seeing them see you
in your face right and you know from the
little that I know of Child Development
the first three years like are
imperative in being able to have like a
parent in your face all the time like
reading you and you're reading the
parents face and then just that that
nervous system that we talked about like
your your child is you're forming your
nervous system related on touch and
affection so if you're not getting that
you feel that for the rest of your life
unless you do like active work yeah to
challenge that and I feel like when
you're on stage and you're as a
performer when you're on stage you
getting that it's like a um it's like a
hit it's like a quick hat version it
makes you feel like you got it but you
didn't really get it and what ends up is
you eventually crash you eventually
crash because you either crash in the
way that he's crashing right now and I
don't want to say it about scrap but
like I know so many men will just blow
up their life yep because they are
trying to like get this feeling that's
not really gonna hold on exactly and or
you crash and you you hit rock bottom
you have a nervous breakdown because you
realize that
everything that is supporting the core
of you is coming from outside of you yep
and when that happens this is someone
who went through this like you you
realize like oh shit like I'm standing
on nothing I've built a house on Sand
and you got to build yourself up from
the ground up and that's a very
difficult thing to do and I know for men
it's especially difficult because the
ego be in the way and you know divorce
feels like failure for a lot oh it
absolutely does and more so for me
because
I I really wanted him like I just wanted
to see him become the best version of
himself and I felt like he was on that
path that path like he was putting in so
much work he was doing so well and then
this moment came and you know that
happened but I do I don't feel like it's
too late for him obviously I want him to
be the best version of himself for our
kids exactly um I want my kids to be
able to look at their dad like you know
he's their hero and
um but yeah it does make me feel bad
though um because I know so much of his
past and how he suffered and all that
kind of stuff but at the same time it's
like we have
endless resources you know what I'm
saying so if we want to get our together
we can
you know
the process of divorce I think for a lot
of people is a mystery mm-hmm
like we hear about it like oh so-and-so
filed for divorce but then you kind of
don't really know what what happens
after that so can you give us some
insight into what your experience has
been for sure so when I first filed for
divorce the that very first day I
started a fast and so this was like a
few days after Thanksgiving
and I fasted through Christmas and New
Year's I just had to focus I was like
I'm not about to be out here drinking
fast do I need to do it yeah you
probably do you should
yeah carry on so um you know I just kind
of like a juice size what kind of fast
well um it was it was like fruits and
vegetables
um I didn't do like meat or alcohol or
like juice or it was just like fruit
vegetables water I just got up to a size
medium I can't I I yeah I don't even
think I lost that much weight during
that time to be honest I mean I was like
eating you're the same person who popped
out three kids and then still the exact
same like I'm just like where wait no I
saw a baby a baby was in there and I was
out here so what happened yeah so um
yeah but through that process it was
just like I had to stay focused I had to
limit my consumption of like social
media and I didn't want to see anything
that he was doing that would like maybe
trigger a reaction or me saying
something online so I just tried to that
was a part of my fast too I was just
like I'm not gonna be on Instagram or
anything like that
um but then it starts to get really real
when you're dealing with like the
divorce and you know we try to do
mediation
to come to agreements but and so the
mediation is around coming to agreements
around money and property and these
types of yes so was there a prenup of
any kind we did not have a prenup was
that a choice or was it just like I mean
would you discuss it or was it just like
we didn't never even discuss it we just
got married and now we just said
um but the great thing was I mean we
didn't really have to divide any like
assets like anything that he had was his
and anything I had was mine
um we didn't have any property together
or anything like that so that part was
easy
um it just
was about figuring out like the
visitation for the kids and yeah
um you know if there was going to be any
child support or anything like that and
when one or both parties are in their
feelings about this whole situation it
makes it hard to come to any sort of
agreement and he was like living in the
house
but he was coming and going as he wanted
to because legally I could not say you
got to get out if I would have told him
he couldn't stay there anymore he would
not have been
obligated to pay any of the bills
anymore and we were like splitting the
bills you know everything was like 50
50. and um how was that
I didn't have a problem with that to be
honest
um but it was It was kind of tough for
me to be able to you know hold the same
weight he was holding like financially
with me being like the mom
um and you know just having to work
differently you know I have to do
different type of work than he does for
the most part you know so um I had some
days where it was very stressful but
anyways like during that time he was
just kind of like here sometimes he
wasn't he came whenever he wanted to and
um
this is the this is the part where it
got a little tricky because on the show
I talked about how he had been late
paying his portion of the rent like a
few times and people took that as me
dragging him or bashing him but it was
just a fact and the owner of the place
that we were living in she was like okay
well we're gonna terminate this lease
because
the payments are coming in late too many
times so I could have had a conversation
with her and said okay he's not going to
be here anymore let me just go ahead and
do this but
my mind was like
if he doesn't pay and I pay I'm gonna
have to like serve him some type of
paper to get him out the house he got
all his stuff like it just would have
been yeah and so I was like okay we're
just gonna move you know but I was upset
I'm not gonna lie like all of my kids
had been in that house since they were
oh yeah you know and um so I was a
little sad I'm just like like you just
you know like it's a lot of like a big
change yeah huge changes and I don't
feel like
um he really realized how big of a
adjustment yeah I'm like you made this
mistake and now our whole entire life
changes you know
so that was like the the hardest part
but once I moved in to my new space with
the kids and we established like some
temporary visitation it made things
easier and then we went to court and we
just got that over with because I know
sometimes divorces they can linger
listen they'd be lasting for like three
years yeah I was like I'm not doing
anything on the paper no
um at the end I wasn't really like
satisfied with the agreement we came to
but that's how much I just wanted it to
be over with I was like I'm not about to
do this any longer
what do you feel like
um
are the things that people say that
around this specific situation that you
want to clear up I heard Rumblings of a
Benzino situation yeah
um
I try hard not to talk about things you
know I'm doing this for you yeah no
that's fine why no because it was a
party yesterday
yeah I feel like off camera I will ask
what was the attraction well
I don't want to be Shady because I felt
like I had said something the other day
and it offended him I said the only
reason people care that I had any type
of dealing with him is because they
don't like how he look right they they
don't like that's not if it was anybody
else they would be like okay well she
just dated him like back in the day like
who cares right but here was the thing
so I'm at Benzino and he's not somebody
that typically I would be attracted to
but he was like a very nice guy and you
know we were hanging out and he was very
very just you know like
and he's fine he was cool okay and so I
hung out with him a few times my friends
we would go to his house he would cook
for us I never slept with him
um but they were filming Love and Hip
Hop this is before I actually like
really got on the show he's like we just
gonna go we're gonna go kick it you know
they're gonna be filming this scene I'm
like all right whatever you know I'm
like down for whatever and so this ended
up becoming like one of the biggest
scenes in the history of Love and Hip
Hop because Kirk was married I didn't
know Kirk right I didn't know Kirk or
Rashida at the time
okay so
um Kirk was married to Rashida she was
pregnant at the time and when I met him
there he said that his wife had given
him a pass to kind of like while out and
do whatever he wanted to do so there
were two other girls who were in the hot
tub and they were on Kirk and I'm like
over here on my side with like Benzino
and we kicking and we talking and the
girls are just like all over Kirk
rubbing on him and so people were mad
they were like oh my God your wife is
pregnant and you know all this and so
I'm over here with Benzino and to be
honest I didn't really
I wasn't really looking at it like that
then but now when I look back I'm like
yeah that was kind of bad you know Bambi
this is two times I mean not that this
not that that's a lot but you be in the
wrong place at the wrong time oh I've
been catching strays
for years and they're just coming back
to back these days but yeah I was in the
wrong place at the wrong time I um
you know if I could do it again like the
part about Benzino like I that's yeah
whatever like we were both single we
were just hanging out but just being in
that environment with the man who was
married and his wife was pregnant yeah
that was a bit much
um but again I didn't know them and he
said his wife gave him a pass I don't
know what the hell kind of I didn't know
what they had going on you know so
there's a lot of there's a lot of
agreements these days that sometimes
like all right if you like it I love it
yeah it is what it is so yeah there's
that um and so every time I'm on any
kind of blog or if I say anything they'd
be like wasn't you in a hot tub with
Benzino and I'd be like yeah
so what that mean what I gotta do
anything and
so what is
what is a part of divorce that you
didn't anticipate
the
sharing of my children
I mean obviously that's something that
has to happen but I didn't really really
think that part through that much like
the fact that my kids are gonna have to
go for days at a time that was like
really scary to me but once I got over
that thought
I was like
let's let's just do it you know what I'm
saying I'm like it's cool you know I'll
be able to get some done for three days
and then boom pop back so okay yeah I
mean I feel like that's a lot of
people's fear yeah you know yeah and
also I feel like a lot of people's fear
is how are my kids going to react yeah
and with that being said I wrote a
children's book about that
um because my son the four-year-old he
was Prince Freeland Prince Freeland yes
he he
didn't understand it like Breeland is so
attached to his dad he follows his dad
around like he will he's on his heels
like all day every day and so um when we
moved out the house we moved into the
new house he kept saying Mommy I want to
go home I want to go home oh and I was
like okay this is our new home and then
he's like no he thought his dad was
still at the other house so that was
like so that was the the roughest part
because I was trying to explain to him
I'm like okay this is gonna be your
house and then you know your dad's gonna
have his own house and then you're gonna
go over there and then you're gonna come
back he's like no I want to go home I
want to go to Alpharetta he would say
that to me I want to go to the house in
Alpharetta and um I'm like yeah no
that's not our home anymore so this
Google phone that we don't know how to
work right just press the side the side
hitting it hitting it yes
so yeah um that was a rough part but um
throughout this process
um writing has been like really
cathartic for me and so okay let's pause
for a second okay baby you're smart
um
I don't know if people know that
you just said cathartic I did you've
been pulling a fast one on us I have
you're smart well Amanda people accuse
me of lying about having a degree or
degrees and I I mean it just doesn't
really
ever come up let's talk about these
degrees Yeah well I mean I have a people
don't just casually throw around
cathartic well well I did because you
know I minored in theater and so that's
when I first started using that word I'm
like oh this is cathartic you know I can
just go in here and just
yeah so yeah impressed are you very
yes tell me more tell me about the
degrees okay so I wanted to I played
basketball right in college a little bit
and I wanted to go to a school that was
division one but I also wanted to
experience like I wanted to do the black
college experience yeah so I went to
Morris Brown that was very short-lived
because once I got there they started
doing the losing their accreditation
yeah and so I played on the team there
for like half the season I broke my hand
and then I moved back home and I just
finished up my degree like really
quickly at Cal State Dominguez okay so
um yeah there was that but
the whole time that I was here in
college it was it was crazy it was
insane because I'm like one of the first
people in my family that has a college
degree and yeah thank you and it was
um I was like homeless some of that time
like sleeping in the car sleeping at
friend's house and all that it's really
important for me to get that you know I
was like let me just do this real quick
I don't know what the hell I'm gonna do
with it but what was your degree in Mass
Communications and I wanted to do public
relations I think I was like one or two
like credits away from public relations
so I just I said yeah let me just do
mass communications okay it's a little
less work but right whatever wrap this
up yeah so um yeah
do you feel like
in the path that you've taken that you
are using your brain to its capacity I
think so
um because when it comes to being a
mother that is like one of the most
important
um parts of my life right now and I'm
very on top of like education for my
children my two little ones they just
started like homeschooling the house I
saw it yeah I got them a teacher and she
comes like four days a week oh dope and
my four-year-old he's in school he's at
this International School where he's
learning Japanese and yeah yeah so I I
feel like um that's Mandarin my bad is
it yeah yeah konichiwa so
um yeah so I'm um I feel like I'm I'm
using it
when it comes to
you know just the way that I deal with
them and you know
um that stuff and now you know I'm an
author you know I published my first
little children's book so I'm not little
yeah it's not little okay big business
but I'm like you know who knows what's
gonna come after this because I have
been writing a lot a lot so yeah
you know it's funny I think a lot of
people when they talk about divorce they
they talk about like how much they lose
but then how much they gain yeah so what
are some things you feel like you're
gaining in this process or have that
um calm nervous system
um
that's priceless so I have gained that
and that's been even before the marriage
and the divorce I was always so like
uptight and you know right now I feel so
calm I feel so relaxed I feel in control
of just everything that is happening in
my life like I don't have anybody to
blame anything on or to be like oh well
you did this so this is why we're in
this position so I just feel really
empowered
that last part resonates the idea of
like there's no one to blame yeah right
I think for some people they would look
at that as a crutch right they would
look at that as like a hitch whereas
like you're you're turning it on its
head and saying no I like that I can
depend on myself and I feel like that's
an empowering strength it absolutely is
like I feel good I know people are like
oh you need to go Hill and I'm like oh
no I dealt with my I was dealing with it
like when it was happening and I I
really recommend that to a lot of people
how were you dealing with it because
that was going to be my next thing like
whatever I was you know crying I was
writing I was working out I was just
really whatever I was feeling I was
feeling it you know I let myself feel it
I let myself and I know a lot of people
too they're like oh you know I don't
want to you know cry in front of the
kids but if at any moment I felt like
that and they were there they were like
are you okay Mommy okay and I'm like
yeah I'm okay okay you know I let myself
kind of go through through it and they
saw it and it was okay it wasn't like
anything I don't feel like it would be
traumatic for them in the future they'll
be like oh my God Mom was just you know
in shambles yeah no so I just if it came
out it just came out and
I think um that was like the best part
how do you feel like your circle showed
up they showed up showed up
um you know people were flying in to
just be around me a lot of my family
they understand how I operate and I
don't always need to be around people
yeah
um so they would call and check in on me
if I wanted to talk
excuse me they would listen and nobody
really
um did too much right when it came to
him or like oh F him and we gonna be
this and you know so they just kind of
like played they position and stayed out
the way and that was really
the support that I needed at the time
because his family was doing a lot and
I'll just tell my family I'm like please
um we we are not doing this with them at
all and so for them to fall back knowing
how much they love me and care about me
it just showed how much they respect me
yeah yeah
I mean how do you feel like being up in
a public relationship like on a TV show
you know played into this uh going in
this direction well it was a lot because
for one I'm not gonna lie like I have a
lot of Pride and maybe if I wasn't no I
still wouldn't
um I just can't
people obviously are watching and so
that magnifies everything especially
like how you
handle people and things but I I just
don't I don't care who I was I I just I
wouldn't have been able to do it because
again like I I do have a lot of Pride
when it comes to I'm like you gonna oh
yeah but do you feel like being in a
public relationship contributed to you
all's problems that even led to this or
do you feel like it would have been
regardless I think it would have been
regardless
um
just because he was like chasing
something that I could not provide for
him
so it didn't really have anything to do
with The public's opinion of it
um
because that's the thing about me to be
honest I'm I'm in trouble right now in a
lot of different areas for just being me
just being like a real friend to people
and I don't really care about how the
public perceives it or whatever I care
about how my friend feels like in real
life yeah so people they don't you know
a lot of people operate off of how they
think the internet is going to react to
something
please speak yes so they'll be like well
I'm not gonna do that because people are
gonna think this and I'll be like well
who are these I don't robots and like
I'm like I'm not it don't even matter
you know what these people think because
when my friend is going through
something or if I'm going through
something my friend is gonna hold me
down and take care of me not the
internet so facts yeah
it's real yeah it's real I mean I think
um
I think the whole process of just
relationships is a lot of us like don't
realize how much effort they require
and I was talking on my Instagram today
just about how like
when we talk about like how
relationships require so much work
majority of the work is work you're
doing on yourself yep it's not even like
necessarily like you with the other
person it's like making sure that you
yourself are the best version of you to
show up in the relationship and that
could be a damage into your relationship
too working on yourself because then you
outgrow your partner and they still just
be like
well I thought you was in therapy and
I'm like I and I am
maybe like triggering you based on the
fact that you are working on yourself
and mind you when you're working on
yourself you're not doing that for the
other person right you're doing that for
you and it's a it's an act of self-love
yeah
and I feel like a lot of folks don't
necessarily put those two things
together they are afraid to go and
either talk to a therapist or go to
Reiki or you know get the workbooks and
explore their mind because they're like
well then that's a weakness or I'm gonna
run into something that I don't want to
run into you know I'm going to uncover
something I don't want to uncover but it
really is an act of self-love it is to
pour into yourself and explore like what
really is going on it here and I cover
the gems on Cut jams and really find
like the stuff that's hidden because so
much of us is hidden beneath the people
have put on us yep and then we get in
these relationships and they put station
on us yes right and then you're like
okay well I've been spending this life
digging my way out of this to get to Joy
and I didn't do that for you to now come
and pour yours on top of me no for real
you know so it's it's really a real
thing when um when we see that the
divorce rates are going up but I feel
like simultaneously the uh the rates of
women going to therapy yeah and women
going into independent spaces is also
going up and absolutely no surprise
that's crazy I I never really looked at
it like that and that that's that's a
real thing because I found out that I
was codependent you know what I'm saying
you know so when you start setting these
boundaries people don't they don't like
it anymore no they're just like oh well
what are we here for then
they don't like the boundary honey they
don't like a no they don't like an
expectation obligation responsibility
they like what's that what is that you
should just be happy I'm here yep yeah
and for a long time you were yeah for
sure I just I really was in all areas of
my life like I don't care if it was
friend like a person on the street like
I got three kids and I'm helping
somebody fold they stroller down and do
you know like I just really feel like I
have to
do extra for people I don't know why we
are very similar see
we I don't we are codependent we just I
don't know what that is either I'm
always like
you need help with that yeah you okay
let me push the card let me carry that
like I'm like why and you know for what
for what it's worth like I think
there's a there's a blessing in that
right because there's a selflessness
with that that I see shows up with your
kids yeah
um and that can really show up in a
great way with a partner who is giving
the same it absolutely did you ever
think about this and this may sound a
little shallow
um did you ever think about like growing
up writing you are beautiful and
um
so just doing too much just because you
wanted people to kind of like not think
that you were like snobby or do you
think that has something to do with you
being so codependent because it's like
you're going out of your way to prove
that you are like cool and human well
yeah because you also you don't want the
light skin thing exactly right so you
don't want to be looked at like oh she
thinks she all like that no she like
skin she could you know you don't want
that yeah you also don't want to like
come off like oh I think I'm better
because I think because that ain't it
either
um and then there's also just the effort
of like I don't want to be judged off of
some surface like I want you to like
Judge Me based off of some real so I
feel like there is an effort that I feel
like I I definitely had I definitely
like consciously made to like do be in
service yeah like how can I be in
service how can I always be in service
you know and I think and I've talked
about this several times on the show
part of the codependent is that you feel
like if you're in service then you'll be
needed yep and then they won't leave you
because you're needed but they will
always leave you
because you just don't you don't no
matter what you have you don't have what
someone oh you don't have enough you
will never have enough never and that's
for you too yeah right like I mean for
all intents and purposes no one has what
I need right only I have what I see and
that's why I have to do the work to find
what I need yeah you know yeah and I'm
so proud of you for you know standing on
just like your own truth and I think a
lot of this being a public figure thing
it can get very murky because folks are
very loud yeah in a way that can make
you question your own truth like you
like yeah I don't wait hold up y'all
don't even know me yeah yeah I don't
know me but I do want to tell you that
you know uh there is a courage to going
through this in front of everybody oh
honey so kudos to you uh I think you
know the whole idea of being in a public
relationship we want to be able to share
yeah you know but you also know that
like on the other side of this
if it go left what they gonna say you
know and you're you would not be human
to not think about that now like you
said you go like okay whatever but
there's still like that piece of you
absolutely and I think mine is more so
for the other person especially now like
dating people
um I always worry about like what they
have seen or heard and how much of that
do they believe and you know so I'm like
this is gonna be weird it's gonna be
weird yeah join the club
um it is going to be weird but what's
not going to be weird is when we go to
our patreon only questions you know I
know y'all got some questions for good
old Bambi right here and I might have a
little surprise for you too oh nice
to uh the seal Squad come on over to the
Amanda verse we got some questions for
bam
you know because everybody in in his
life at the time was the problem
everyone was the problem and I was like
well if he just had someone who was not
the problem who didn't have those
qualities then he would be a better
person and that's like you know
that's tough man yeah
um okay someone asked was there anything
scrap could have done to make you stop
the divorce process
the fact that people think that oh you
have to have a healthy co-parent I'm
like no we're gonna parallel parents
because I don't fuck with him like that
and
did you know that you subscribed no
I did not
um well if you didn't hear the questions
in the bonus section you need to go
ahead you need to go check them out
because this is a piggyback off of that
but you know you said you don't
co-parent you parallel parent what is
that so for me parallel parenting is
just everything that we communicate
about it is very
matter effect and it's about the kids
and that's it like it's nothing outside
of that like I don't care
how you doing I don't you know what I'm
saying I don't care who you dating who
you with who you got the kids around
like it's not my concern unless I feel
like my kids are like effective yeah and
so I don't care about none of that like
I don't care
about anything it's just the garage goes
up the kids go out and if there's
anything in between that I need to know
about then you can let me know and I'll
do the same but we're not doing birthday
parties together at least not right now
like I was gonna say I feel like this
will like
as they get older they are gonna want
y'all together in certain spaces because
they're going to see their friends yeah
you know I can coexist I don't I don't
mind that I can go to recital you just
got to sit next to each other yeah we
don't got to sit next to each other but
you know I'm cool but I I'm not about to
be like fake oh yeah I'm cool with all
my baby mamas like nigga no I'm not the
no we're not friends you can go do what
you do with the rest of them but yeah
well you know what they say they say
that eventually the anger turns into
compassion yeah and that that's the way
that we we heal uh I guess the number
one question is how are you doing
well I feel great like I I really truly
think I'm doing good until I get on the
internet and people say you need to go
heal and I'll be like what I thought I
thought I was I mean healing is a
process I feel like that's the other
thing everyone has to go through that
process differently yeah but I feel like
when you talk about making concerted
efforts to you know indulge in the
feeling and not try and you know because
black women you know we love to be
strong do the feeling
not don't cry out I'm gonna cry I'm
gonna cry and I'm gonna cry a lot and
I'm Gonna Keep crying until I Ain't Got
No More Tears and that's kind of where
I'm at right now like I feel great you
know I feel really good for real like I
can actually like
be in another relationship if I wanted
to that's how like you know we love that
for you yeah we love that for you and
you know I think the people that are
listening and watching who have you know
been through a divorce who are
contemplating a divorce or going through
a divorce like they want to be where you
are yeah and I think when we share our
stories and we talk about you know the
the highs and the lows of these types of
scenarios it really does encourage
people to know that they can find what's
within them to get to the peaceful place
that you're at I'm nervous yeah for sure
and I I do encourage people to stay and
try to work it out and fight it out
especially if you have something to
fight for I just you know
at my in my situation like it was it
came to a point where I didn't have
anything to fight for so you know but if
you can still fight if your partner is
making efforts as well I feel like fight
fight fight
All We Got Is Us
thanks Dan thank you
[Music]